A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Office of the Arts, Program Files FA640
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Visual Arts Grants, 1958-1959; XIV
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Bardin, J., 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Berge, Dorothy, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Bireline, George, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Burford, Byron, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Driesbach, David F., 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Elshin, Jacob, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Fink, Herbert, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Gates, Robert, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Goldin, Leon, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Gussow, Roy, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Heliker, John, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Horiuchi, Paul, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Ivey, William, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Kahn, Max, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Martin, Keith M., 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Morris, Carl, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Myers, Malcolm, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Sussman, Richard N., 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Tremain, Joyce, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Umlauf, Charles, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Purchase Awards -- Von Wicht, John, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Background, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Expenses, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Forms, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grant Actions, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Jurors, Final Meeting, Jan 10, 1959 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominees A-H, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominees I-Z, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Jurors, Regional -- Regions 1-6, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Jurors, Regional -- Regions 7-12, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominees Ineligible, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Possible Jurors, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Press Releases and Fact Sheet, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominators Corresponence A-H, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominators Correspondence I-Z, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Statistics, 1958 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Jurors' Declinations, 1959 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Jurors, Final (Correspondence), 1959 (Box 66)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Registration Cards -- Award Winners and Participating Artists (sampling), 1959 (Box 66)
- Reference Materials, Statistical Data, Tabulations and Worksheets, 1954; XV
  - College Grants Program Chronology -- Committee Staff Tabulations (1/2), undated (Box 67)
  - College Grants Program Chronology -- Committee Staff Tabulations (2/2), undated (Box 67)
  - College Grants Program -- Statistics Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 67)
  - College Grants Program -- Miscellaneous Committee Staff Tabulations, undated (Box 67)
  - College Grants Program -- Tabulations Miscellaneous, undated (Box 67)
  - College Grants Program -- Work Sheets Miscellaneous, undated (Box 67)
- Grantee Media Files, 1965-1979; XVI
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Video, film and audio tape.
  - Symphony Orchestra Recordings, 1965 November-1966 April; XVI.1
    - New York Philharmonic, 1965 November 1 (Box 70, Reel AV 5015)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Amyas Ames, President, Carlos Moseley, Managing Director, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Philadelphia Orchestra Association, 1965 November 1 (Box 70, Reel AV 5016)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: C. Wanton Balis, Jr., President, Boris Sokoloff, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 2 (Box 70, Reel AV 5017)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Henry B. Cabot, president, Thomas D. Perry Jr., Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1965 November 2 (Box 70, Reel AV 5018)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: J.B. Koepfli, President, W. Severns, Chief Administrator, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - National Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 3 (Box 70, Reel AV 5019)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: L. Symington, First Vice President, M. Robert Rogers, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Baltimore Symphony, 1965 November 4 (Box 70, Reel AV 5020)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: J. Meyerhoff, President, O. Lobanov, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Cincinnati Symphony, 1965 November 4 (Box 70, Reel AV 5021)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: L.L. Davis, President, L.H. Haldeman, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Cleveland Orchestra, 1965 November 8 (Box 70, Reel AV 5022)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: F. E. Joseph, President, A.B. Barksdale, Manager, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 8 (Box 70, Reel AV 5023)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Merrill Shepard, President, Silas Edman, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra Society, 1965 November 9 (Box 70, Reel AV 5024)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Clarence Obletz, President, Symour Rosen, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra, 1965 November 9 (Box 70, Reel AV 5025)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Frank E. Holley, President, Thomas (No Suggestions), Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Indianapolis Symphony, 1965 November 10 (Box 70, Reel AV 5026)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Clarence Elbert, President, Hubert Scott, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - St. Louis Symphony, 1965 November 10 (Box 70, Reel AV 5027)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Stanley J. Goodman, President, L. Gerdine, Acting Manager, Sigmund Koch, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Minneapolis Symphony, 1965 November 11 (Box 70, Reel AV 5028)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Judson Bemis, President, Kenneth Dayton, Executive Committee, Richard M. Cisek, Managing Director, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Kansas City Philharmonic, 1965 November 11 (Box 70, Reel AV 5029)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: John M. Phillips, President, Peter Pastreich, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - New Orleans Philharmonic, 1965 November 12 (Box 70, Reel AV 5030)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: D. Blair Fabrot, Treasurer, Thomas A. Greene, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Symphony Society of San Antonio, 1965 November 12 (Box 70, Reel AV 5031)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Edward C. Sullivan, President, Mrs. Edgar Tobin, Member of Board, Kenneth K. Caswell, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Dallas Symphony, 1965 November 15 (Box 70, Reel AV 5032)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Ralph B. Rogers, President, Alan Watrous, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Denver Symphony, 1965 November 16 (Box 70, Reel AV 5033)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Charles S. Sterne, President, Mark P. Huber, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - San Francisco Symphony, 1965 November 16 (Box 70, Reel AV 5034)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Philip S. Boone, President, Joseph A. Scafidi, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Society, 1965 November 17 (Box 70, Reel AV 5035)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Charles Denby, President, John S. Edwards, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 17 (Box 70, Reel AV 5036)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Robert Semple, President, Howard Harrington, Manager, Ralph T. McElvenny, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 18 (Box 70, Reel AV 5037)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Charles L. Towers, President, Leslie C. White, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Houston Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 18 (Box 70, Reel AV 5038)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: General Maurice Hirsch, President, Tom M. Johnson, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - San Diego Symphony, 1965 November 19 (Box 70, Reel AV 5039)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Philip M. Klauber, President, William L. Denton, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 19 (Box 70, Reel AV 5040)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Paul P. Ashley, President, Mrs. Hugh E. McCreery, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Hartford Symphony, 1965 November 22 (Box 70, Reel AV 5041)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: C.E. Lord, President, David Kent, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - American Symphony Orchestra, 1965 November 22 (Box 70, Reel AV 5042)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Samuel Rubin, President, S. Warkow, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Brooklyn Philharmonia, 1965 November 23 (Box 70, Reel AV 5043)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: M.L. Koeppel, President, M.P. Ladin, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - New Jersey Symphony, 1965 November 23 (Box 70, Reel AV 5044)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: H.P. Becton, President, A.A. Pinsker, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - New Haven Symphony, 1965 November 24 (Box 70, Reel AV 5045)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: B.C. Cannon, President, Harold Kendrick, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Rhode Island Philharmonic, 1965 November 24 (Box 70, Reel AV 5046)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: R. W. Billings, President, Mrs. Mueriel Stevens, Acting Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Festival Orchestra Society, 1965 November 29 (Box 70, Reel AV 5047)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Stephen Benedict, President, W. Price, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Syracuse Symphony, 1965 November 29 (Box 70, Reel AV 5048)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Mrs. P.A. Hopkins Jr., President, Benson E. Snyder, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Little Orchestra Society, 1965 November 30 (Box 70, Reel AV 5049)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Thomas Scherman, Music Director, Herbert Barrett, Manager, Marks Levine, Treasurer and Assistant Secretary, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Louisville Orchestra, 1965 November 30 (Box 70, Reel AV 5050)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Dr. R.J. Noer, President, Richard H. Wangerin, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Honolulu Symphony, 1965 November 30 (Box 71, Reel AV 5051)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: John F. Murphy, President, Marshall W. Turkin, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Columbus Symphony, 1965 December 1 (Box 71, Reel AV 5052)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: A. Fullerton Miller, Chairman, A.W. McCracken, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Marcia Thompson.
    - Greater Miami Philharmonic, 1965 December 1 (Box 71, Reel AV 5053)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: E.J. Gould, President, Henry Peltier, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Fort Wayne Philharmonic, 1965 December 2 (Box 71, Reel AV 5054)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: J.F. Anglin, President, N. Greenberg, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Toledo Orchestra, 1965 December 2 (Box 71, Reel AV 5055)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: C.C. Dybvig, President, D.C. Barnette, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Kalamazoo Symphony Society, 1965 December 3 (Box 71, Reel AV 5056)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Cameron L. Davis, Chairman, W.D. Brownell, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Wichita Symphony, 1965 December 3 (Box 71, Reel AV 5057)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Arthur G. Harrell, President, D. Anderson, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Richmond Symphony, 1965 December 6 (Box 71, Reel AV 5058)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Edmund A. Rennolds, Chairman of the Board, A.H. Thompson, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Omaha Symphony, 1965 December 6 (Box 71, Reel AV 5059)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: John M. Harding, President, James Emde, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Nashville Symphony, 1965 December 7 (Box 71, Reel AV 5060)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: L.J. Mulhall, President and Board Chairman, R.R. Mackenzie, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Birmingham Symphony, 1965 December 8 (Box 71, Reel AV 5061)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: A.S. Lacy, President, H.T. Heath, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Florida Symphony, 1965 December 8 (Box 71, Reel AV 5062)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: R.T. Anderson, President, Miss Helen E. Ryan, Executive Vice President and Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Portland Symphony Society, 1965 December 10 (Box 71, Reel AV 5063)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Dr. F.H. Bentley, President, R.P. Thomson, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Milwaukee Symphony, 1965 December 10 (Box 71, Reel AV 5064)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: C.A. Randall, President, R.S. Zigman, Manager, William R. Johnson, Board Member, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Utah Symphony Orchestra, 1965 December 13 (Box 71, Reel AV 5065)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Wendell J. Ashton, General V.P., Obert C. Tanner, Board Member, H.L. Gregory, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Phoenix Symphony Orchestra, 1965 December 13 (Box 71, Reel AV 5066)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Lewis J. Ruskin, Board Chairman, William C. Turner, President, D. Richards, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Tampa Philharmonic Orchestra, 1965 December 14 (Box 71, Reel AV 5067)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Eugene B. Dodson, President, D. Ramsay, Manager, James W. Gray Jr., Board Member, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Tulsa Philharmonic Society, Inc., 1965 December 14 (Box 71, Reel AV 5068)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Burch Mayo, President, Frederick Peters, Board Member, Herbert Gussman, Board Member, Mrs. W. Gillette, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Sacramento Symphony, 1965 December 15 (Box 71, Reel AV 5069)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: C.B. Swanson, President, Mrs. G.S. Fisher, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Oakland Symphony, 1965 December 15 (Box 71, Reel AV 5070)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Edgar F. Kaiser, Chairman, J. Allen Bray, President, Michael Miller, Board Member, R. Kelligar, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Oklahoma City Symphony, 1965 December 17 (Box 71, Reel AV 5071)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: W.B. Cleary, President, Frank Ratka, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Hudson Valley Philharmonic, 1966 January 13 (Box 71, Reel AV 5072)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Mrs. Sidney M. Miller, President, Mrs. Helen Kronenfild, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Jacksonville Symphony, 1966 January 17 (Box 71, Reel AV 5073)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Hugh Abernethy, President, Mrs. Dorothe Tunstall, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Memphis Symphony, 1966 January 17 (Box 71, Reel AV 5074)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Eric A. Catmur, President, Robert MacIntyre, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - North Carolina Symphony, 1966 January 18 (Box 71, Reel AV 5075)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Benjamin Swalin, Directory, Victor S. Bryant, Board Member, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Dayton Philharmonic, 1966 January 19 (Box 71, Reel AV 5076)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Thomas Munroe, First Vice President, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Shreveport Symphony, 1966 January 19 (Box 71, Reel AV 5077)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Hall M. Lyons, President, John Shenaut, Conductor, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Springfield Symphony, Massachusetts, 1966 January 20 (Box 71, Reel AV 5078)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Wallace Burnett, President, Terry C. Schwarz, Manager, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Orchestra Da Camera, 1966 January 31 (Box 71, Reel AV 5079)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Mrs. Flori Lorr, Executive Director, Ralph Lorr, Personnel Manager, George F. Baker, Member of Board, Mr. Luis Bejerano, Director of Development, Hofstra, Fr. Rowe, Chairman of Music Department, Hofstra, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson, George Kuyper, Consultant.
    - Symphony Orchestra of Puerto Rico, 1966 February 25 (Box 71, Reel AV 5080)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Ademar Toro, Executive Vice President, Maurice J. Phillips, Public Relations Officer of the Economic Development of Administration of Puerto Rico, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
    - Westchester Symphony Orchestra, 1966 April 11 (Box 71, Reel AV 5081)
      Place: Ford Foundation offices. Present: Mrs. Thelma Rost, Member of Board of Directors, Raphael B. Malsin, President, Sigmund Koch, Edward F. D'Arms, Marcia Thompson.
  - Kodaly Music Program -- Holy Names College -- Final Concert, 1974; Cassette tapes, 4 tapes
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file, and are not yet stablized. Once the material has been stablized by RAC archival staff, it will be assigned a unique separation number. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    Conditions Governing Access
    See also: Ford Foundation grant 07300588 (PA73-588), Holy Names College, PARTIAL SUPPORT OF AN ACADEMIC PROGRAM IN KODALY BASED MUSICAL TRAINING.
    - Kodaly Summer Program, 1975; 1/2" Open reel (Tape AV 10026)
      Original Composition by Grahm Johnson and Summer Course Participants.
    - Margaret Holden Class: Principles and Practices, Summer 1974; 1/2" Open reel (Tape AV 10027)
      Tape #3
    - Final Concert, Summer 1974; 1/2" Open reel (Tape AV 10028)
      Tape #2
    - Final Concert, Summer 1974; 1/2" Open reel (Tape AV 10029)
      Tape #1
  - Excerpts from Rhythemetron with the Dance Theater of Harlem and Arthur Mitchell, Nov 30, 1977; 23 minutes (Tape AV 10016)
    RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - Excerpts from Rhythemetron with the Dance Theater of Harlem and Arthur Mitchell / Dance on a May Day with Jacques d'Amboise, 30 November 1977; 2012:078:014; 17 minutes. (Tape AV 10017)
    Version 2.
  - Out of Our Father's House -- The American National Theatre and Academy, 1979; 60 minutes. (Tape AV 10038)
    See also: Ford Foundation grant 07800276 (PA78-276), The American National Theatre And Academy, Inc., PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR DEVELOPMENT OF THE TECHNOLOGY FOR VIDEO-TAPING STAGED PLAYS.
  - Ford Foundation -- National Dance Institute -- Dance on a May Day, Dec 2, 1977; 3/4" Umatic (Tape AV 10013)
  - Abstraction -- Roemer-Young Associates, 1971; Sound, Color, 9 minutes. (Reel AV 1957, Reel AV 2004)
    All inquires to view films require advanced notice of at least 24 hours, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those not available in modern formats, may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
    Separated to Ford Foundation Film collection.
    Scope and Contents note
    Short film presented by the American Federation of Arts about the physics and characteristics of abstraction. Distorting physical items from science, nature, and intangible items in math and art can all be understood as abstraction. Abstract concepts in design, art, and language are shown. An ACI Release.